就是这样的
And, that's it.
我们实现了ContentProvider
We finished creating our ContentProvider.
既然这是个互动的环节  那我们就来说说所实现的代码
Since this has been an involved section, let's talk about what we created.
我们首先定义了ContentProvider所支持的URI
We started off by defining the URI's that our ContentProvider will support.
然后更新了合约来对应这些URI
We then updated our contract to reflect these URIs.
我们创建了一个URIMatcher  用来将URI和常量进行对应
From there, we built a URIMatcher that matches these URIs to constants we use
这些常量会在其它请求ContentProvider的函数中用在switch条件判断中
in switch statements in all of the other required content provider functions.
然后我们实现了getType方法为每个URI返回
Then we implemented the getType function to return the type of
游标（Cursor）的类型
cursor returned for each URI.
然后我们实现了ContentProvider查询函数
We then implemented the ContentProvider query functions,
紧接着实现了写操作包括插入  更新  和删除
followed by the write operations insert, update, and delete.
最后  我们聊了一下bulkInsert函数
Finally, we talked about the optional BulkInsert
它在一个单独会话中更新数据库
function to make updates to our database in a single transaction.
和多会话下更新数据库相比  这种方式运行更快
This performs much faster, and causes less wear and tear on the flash chip,
并且能够减少闪存芯片的损耗
compared to updating the database in multiple transaction.
Android的开源世界中有很多库
There are lots of libraries out there in the Android open source
可用来创建ContentProvider
world to help you built ContentProviders.
如果你想要使用它们  你就得先知道它们
If you want to use them, you'll be able to use them now
的工作原理  和他们的具体功能
with the confidence that you know how they work, and what they are doing.
所以所有对数据库
So all queries and
的请求和更新可以通过ContentProvider接口来实现
updates to the database can now be done through the ContentProvider interface.
但是我们的代码中还没用到
But, we're still not using it in our code.
让我们把它加上
Let's fix that.